export const PROBLEM_OF_MONTH_2016 = [
    {
        month: "January",
        year: 2016,
        question: "1512q.pdf",
        solution: "1601a.pdf",
        solvers: [
            { name: "Toshihiro Shimizu", affiliation: "Kawasaki, Japan" },
            { name: "Tomas Jurik", affiliation: "Kosice, Slovakia" },
            { name: "Hasan Zubeyr Demir", affiliation: "Ozel Caglayan Fen Lisesi, Ankara" },
            { name: "Harald Bögeholz", affiliation: "c't Computer Magazine,  Germany" },
            { name: "Roger Bengtsson", affiliation: "Lund, Sweden" },
            { name: "Andreas Stiller", affiliation: "c't Computer Magazine,  Germany" },
            { name: "Albert Stadler", affiliation: "Herrliberg, Switzerland" }
        ]
    },

    {
        month: "February",
        year: 2016,
        question: "1601q.pdf",
        solution: "1602a.pdf",
        solvers: [
            { name: "Toshihiro Shimizu", affiliation: "Kawasaki, Japan" },
            { name: "Wong Chi Fung", affiliation: "Hong Kong" },
            { name: "Vedat Deveçi", affiliation: "DMI, Istanbul" },
            { name: "Gruian Cornel", affiliation: "Cluj-Napoca, Romania" },
            { name: "Albert Stadler", affiliation: "Herrliberg , Switzerland" },
            { name: "Shatlyk Mamedov", affiliation: "School 21, Dashoguz, Turkmenistan" },
            { name: "Michel Bataille", affiliation: "Rouen, France" },
            { name: "Mohammad Reza Yegan", affiliation: "Central Tehran Branch, Islamic Azad University, Iran" },
            { name: "Magnus Jakobsson", affiliation: "Lund, Sweden" },
            { name: "Oskar Volpatti", affiliation: "Como, Italy" },
            { name: "Tomas Jurik", affiliation: "Kosice, Slovakia" }
        ]
    },

    {
        month: "March",
        year: 2016,
        question: "1602q.pdf",
        solution: "1603a.pdf",
        solvers: [
            { name: "Toshihiro Shimizu", affiliation: "Kawasaki, Japan" },
            { name: "Harald Bogeholz", affiliation: "c't Computer magazine, Germany" },
            { name: "Hasan Zubeyr Demir", affiliation: "Ozel Caglayan Fen Lisesi, Ankara" },
            { name: "Albert Stadler", affiliation: "Herrliberg , Switzerland" },
            { name: "Feyza Duman", affiliation: "Özel Servergazi Fen Lisesi, Denizli" },
            { name: "Magnus Jakobsson", affiliation: "Lund, Sweden" },
            { name: "Cemre Çadır", affiliation: "İzmir Fen Lisesi, İzmir" },
            { name: "Gulbuddin H. Al Akbar", affiliation: "Ankara, Turkey" },
            { name: "Arthur Vause", affiliation: "Preston, Lancashire, U.K." },
            { name: "Mohammad Reza Yegan", affiliation: "Central Tehran Branch, Islamic Azad University, Iran" },
            { name: "Lim Chang Kiat", affiliation: "Malaysia" },
            { name: "Roger Bengtsson", affiliation: "Lund, Sweden" },
            { name: "Gruian Cornel", affiliation: "Cluj-Napoca, Romania" },
            { name: "Serkan Sonel", affiliation: "Bilkent University, Ankara" },
            { name: "Tomas Jurik", affiliation: "Kosice, Slovakia" },
            { name: "Ernist Tilenbaev", affiliation: "TOBB University" },
            { name: "Can Türkün", affiliation: "TOBB University" }
        ]
    },

    {
        month: "April",
        year: 2016,
        question: "1603q.pdf",
        solution: "1604a.pdf",
        solvers: [
            { name: "Toshihiro Shimizu", affiliation: "Kawasaki, Japan" },
            { name: "Kayra Uygun", affiliation: "Ankara Fen Lisesi" },
            { name: "Tomas Jurik", affiliation: "Kosice, Slovakia" },
            { name: "Hasan Zubeyr Demi", affiliation: "Ozel Caglayan Fen Lisesi, Ankara" },
            { name: "Feyza Duman", affiliation: "Özel Servergazi Fen Lisesi, Denizli" },
            { name: "Roger Bengtsson", affiliation: "Lund, Sweden" }
        ]
    },

    {
        month: "May",
        year: 2016,
        question: "1604q.pdf",
        solution: "1605a.pdf",
        solvers: [
            { name: "Toshihiro Shimizu", affiliation: "Kawasaki, Japan" },
            { name: "Arthur Vause", affiliation: "Preston, Lancashire, U.K." },
            { name: "Magnus Jakobsson", affiliation: "Lund, Sweden" },
            { name: "Ahmet İleri", affiliation: "Özel Yamanlar Fen lisesi, İzmir" },
            { name: "Eray Ünsal Atay", affiliation: "İzmir Özel Fatih Koleji" },
            { name: "Nurullah Giray Kuru", affiliation: "İstanbul Erkek Lisesi" },
            { name: "Ömer Avcı", affiliation: "Özel Yamanlar Fen Lisesi, İzmir" },
            { name: "Kayra Uygun", affiliation: "Ankara Fen Lisesi" },
            { name: "Gulbuddin H. Al Akbar", affiliation: "Ankara, Turkey" },
            { name: "Tomas Jurik", affiliation: "Kosice, Slovakia" }
        ]
    },

    {
        month: "June",
        year: 2016,
        question: "1605q.pdf",
        solution: "1606a.pdf",
        solvers: [
            { name: "Toshihiro Shimizu", affiliation: "Kawasaki, Japan" },
            { name: "Gulbuddin H. Al Akbar", affiliation: ".Ankara, Turkey" },
            { name: "Albert Stadler", affiliation: "Herrliberg , Switzerland" },
            { name: "Ömer Avcı", affiliation: "Yamanlar Fen lisesi, İzmir" },
            { name: "Vedat Deveci", affiliation: "DMO Istanbul" },
            { name: "Tomas Jurik", affiliation: "Kosice, Slovakia" },
            { name: "Onur Sulak", affiliation: "Samanyolu Lisesi, Ankara" },
            { name: "Mehmet Berke İşler", affiliation: "Özel Servergazi Fen Lisesi, Denizli" },
            { name: "Muhammetnur Bagbekov", affiliation: "School 21, Dashoguz, Turkmenistan" },
            { name: "Ozan Kaymak", affiliation: "Özel Servergazi Fen Lisesi, Denizli" },
            { name: "Mehmet Selaheddin Şentop", affiliation: "İstanbul Erkek Lisesi" },
            { name: "Osman Berat Yıldırım", affiliation: "Özel Antalya Toros Akdeniz Fen Lisesi" },
            { name: "Hasan Yasin Çetin", affiliation: "Ankara Özel Atlantik Fen Lisesi" },
            { name: "Michel Bataille", affiliation: "Rouen, France" },
            { name: "Ivane Gokadze", affiliation: "Georgıa" },
            { name: "Vincelot Ravoson", affiliation: "Lycee Henri IV, Paris, France" },
            { name: "Furkan Suluova", affiliation: "Hacettepe University" },
            { name: "Laçin Can ATIŞ", affiliation: "İstanbul, Turkey" }
        ]
    },

    {
        month: "July-August",
        year: 2016,
        question: "1606q.pdf",
        solution: "1608a.pdf",
        solvers: [
            { name: "Toshihiro Shimizu", affiliation: "Kawasaki, Japan" },
            { name: "Murad Sapayew", affiliation: ".School 21, Dashoguz, Turkmenistan" },
            { name: "Shatlyk Mamedov", affiliation: "Dashoguz, Turkmenistan" },
            { name: "Hasan Zubeyr Demir", affiliation: "Özel Ankara Çağlayan Fen Lisesi, Ankara" },
            { name: "Murat Chashemov", affiliation: "TSU, Turkmenistan" },
            { name: "Vincelot Ravoson", affiliation: "Lycee Henri IV, Paris, France" },
            { name: "Albert Stadler", affiliation: "Herrliberg , Switzerland" },
            { name: "Laçin Can Atış", affiliation: "İstanbul, Turkey" },
            { name: "Lamis Al Sheikh", affiliation: "Bordeaux, France" },
            { name: "Roger Bengtsson", affiliation: "Lund, Sweden" },
            { name: "Adem Limani", affiliation: "Lund, Sweden" },
            { name: "Tomas Jurik", affiliation: "Kosice Slovakia" }
        ]
    },

    {
        month: "September",
        year: 2016,
        question: "1608q.pdf",
        solution: "1609a.pdf",
        solvers: [
            { name: "Toshihiro Shimizu", affiliation: "Kawasaki, Japan" },
            { name: "Hasan Zubeyr Demir", affiliation: "Özel Ankara Çağlayan Fen Lisesi, Ankara" },
            { name: "Feyza Duman", affiliation: "Boğaziçi University" },
            { name: "İhsan Mert Atalay", affiliation: "Boğaziçi University" },
            { name: "Arthur Vause", affiliation: "Preston, Lancashire, U.K." },
            { name: "Tomas Jurik", affiliation: "Kosice, Slovakia" },
            { name: "Lim Chang Kiat", affiliation: "Malaysia" }
        ]
    },

    {
        month: "October",
        year: 2016,
        question: "1609q.pdf",
        solution: "1610a.pdf",
        solvers: [
            { name: "Toshihiro Shimizu", affiliation: "Kawasaki, Japan" },
            { name: "Vedat Deveci", affiliation: "DMO İstanbul" },
            { name: "Steffen Weber", affiliation: "Ismanıng, Germany" },
            { name: "Tomas Jurik", affiliation: "Kosice, Slovakia" }
        ]
    },

    {
        month: "November",
        year: 2016,
        question: "1610q.pdf",
        solution: "1611a.pdf",
        solvers: [
            { name: "Toshihiro Shimizu", affiliation: "Kawasaki, Japan" },
            { name: "Tomas Jurik", affiliation: "Kosice Slovakia" },
            { name: "Sapar Saryyev", affiliation: "Bilkent University" },
            { name: "Albert Stadler", affiliation: "Herrliberg , Switzerland" },
            { name: "F. Walner", affiliation: "Germany" },
            { name: "Gocha Gokadze", affiliation: "L.T.D. School 1 Georgia," },
            { name: "Ivane Gokadze", affiliation: "L.T.D. School 1 Georgia" },
            { name: "Vivek Mehra", affiliation: "Mumbai, India" },
            { name: "Henrik Aberg", affiliation: "Gothenburg, Sweden" },
            { name: "Hasan Zubeyr Demir", affiliation: "Ozel Caglayan Fen Lisesi, Ankara" },
            { name: "Paolo Perfetti", affiliation: "University of Rome Tor Vergata, Italy" },
            { name: "Michel Bataille", affiliation: "Rouen, France" },
            { name: "Mehmet Ali Yildirim", affiliation: "Florya Final Anadolu Lisesi, Istanbul" },
            { name: "Adem Limani", affiliation: "Lund, Sweden" },
            { name: "Roger Bengtsson", affiliation: "Lund, Sweden" },
            { name: "Laçin Can Atış", affiliation: "Istanbul" }
        ]
    },

    {
        month: "December",
        year: 2016,
        question: "1611q.pdf",
        solution: "1612a.pdf",
        solvers: [
            { name: "Toshihiro Shimizu", affiliation: "Kawasaki, Japan" },
            { name: "Mehmet Ali Yildirim", affiliation: "Florya Final Anadolu Lisesi, Istanbul" },
            { name: "Tomas Jurik", affiliation: "Kosice, Slovakia" },
            { name: "Abdulkadir Tanrıverdi", affiliation: "Eskişehir" },
            { name: "Henrik Aberg", affiliation: "Gothenburg, Sweden" },
            { name: "Burak Can Biner", affiliation: "Bilkent University" },
            { name: "Roger Bengtsson", affiliation: "Lund, Sweden" }
        ]
    }
];
